{"question_list":[{"question":{"ID":"4","Question":"Which of the following is <br><u>NOT<\/u><\/b> an event in the ABAP\/4 programming language","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 00:07:11","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"End-of-initialization","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 00:07:11"},{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"End-of-selection","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 00:07:11"},{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Get","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 00:07:11"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 00:07:11"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"4","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 00:07:11"}]},{"question":{"ID":"5","Question":"What type of memory is typically used as to save defaullt values for screen fields","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"5","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"SAP-Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-06-25 01:26:26"},{"QuestionId":"5","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"ABAP\/4 Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-06-25 01:26:26"},{"QuestionId":"5","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Shared Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-06-25 01:26:43"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"5","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-06-25 01:26:53"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"5","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-06-24 10:30:00"}]},{"question":{"ID":"6","Question":"Select the valid customer defined message","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"MESSAGE Y123","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:18:17"},{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"MESSAGE E123(9999).","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:18:17"},{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"MESSAGE ID 'AT' TYPE 'S' NUMBER 100","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:18:55"},{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"MESSAGE E123 by Fielda Fieldb","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:18:55"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:19:33"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"6","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:20:34"}]},{"question":{"ID":"7","Question":"What happens when a 1 to many relationship is encountered with an inner join","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Redundant data is not returned to the resultant set","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:22:59"},{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Redundant data from the outer table is included","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:22:59"},{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Run time error","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:24:05"},{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Redundant data from the inner table is included","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:24:05"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:24:38"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"7","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DB","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:25:31"}]},{"question":{"ID":"8","Question":"What must be assigned to Search Helps","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Data Element","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:26:51"},{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Domain","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:26:51"},{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Values","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:27:35"},{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Nothing","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:27:35"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:28:30"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"8","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DDIC","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:28:55"}]},{"question":{"ID":"9","Question":"What is contained in variable SY-LINSZ","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Row count of the current line","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:34:41"},{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Height of the current line","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:34:41"},{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Width of the current line","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:35:45"},{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"No of characters in the current line","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:35:45"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:35:59"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"9","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 01:36:32"}]},{"question":{"ID":"13","Question":"What is true about the primary index of the table","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"13","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"The primary index is automatically created when the table is activated","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:36:13"},{"QuestionId":"13","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"The key fields of the table make up the primary index","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:36:13"},{"QuestionId":"13","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The primary index ID is designated by the Database Adminstrator","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:36:13"},{"QuestionId":"13","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"The developer designates the fields to be used as the primary index","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:36:13"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"13","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:36:13"},{"QuestionId":"13","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:36:13"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"13","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DDIC","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:36:13"}]},{"question":{"ID":"12","Question":"What determines if a table is client specific or client independent","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"The first field is mandt with a external data type CLNT and specified as a key field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-01 00:41:02"},{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Depends how Basis has configured the client","CreatedAt":"2013-07-01 00:41:02"},{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"The first field is mandt with a domain CLNT but not specified as a key field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-01 00:41:02"},{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The option 'Client Specified' is added to the Select statement","CreatedAt":"2013-07-01 00:43:23"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-01 00:41:02"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"12","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DDIC","CreatedAt":"2013-07-01 00:41:02"}]},{"question":{"ID":"14","Question":"Default page headings are created on which list types","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"14","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"All Lists","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:37:55"},{"QuestionId":"14","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Basic Lists","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:37:55"},{"QuestionId":"14","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Secondary Lists","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:37:55"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"14","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:37:55"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"14","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:37:55"}]},{"question":{"ID":"15","Question":"Program A issues the following statement: SUBMIT PROGRAM B.\n<br>\nSelect the correct statement","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Program A becomes active in the same internal session of Program B","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:41:41"},{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Program B becomes active in the same internal session of Program A","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:41:41"},{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"User Context is flushed","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:41:41"},{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Program B runs in a new internal session","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:41:41"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:41:41"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"15","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:41:41"}]},{"question":{"ID":"16","Question":"If there are no entries in <b>itab<\/b> then what is the result of the following select:\n<br>\n<b>Select * from DBTAB for all entries in itab where key1 = itab-key1.<\/b>","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Run time error","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:45:59"},{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"All entries from DBTAB are retrieved","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:45:59"},{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Only distinct values for key1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:45:59"},{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"No entries are retrieved","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:45:59"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:45:59"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"16","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:45:59"}]},{"question":{"ID":"17","Question":"What conditions apply for a LEFT OUTER JOIN in OPEN SQL","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"17","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Only OR can be used as a logical operator in the ON condition","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:48:09"},{"QuestionId":"17","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"A Left Outer Join is not permitted in OPEN SQL","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:48:09"},{"QuestionId":"17","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"A join statement is found to the right of the join operator","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:48:09"},{"QuestionId":"17","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"At least one field frorm the table on the right is required for comparison in the ON condition","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:48:09"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"17","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:48:09"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"17","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DDIC","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:48:09"}]},{"question":{"ID":"18","Question":"What is needed to ensure that a check field is verified against the referenced key field of the check table","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"same data type only is required for check field and referenced field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:51:35"},{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"all key fields MUST have domain equality between check table and foreign key table","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:51:35"},{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"same domain is required for check field and referenced field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:51:35"},{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"same data element is required for check field and referenced field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:51:35"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:51:35"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"18","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DDIC","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:51:35"}]},{"question":{"ID":"19","Question":"What is an example of Organizational Data","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Sales Order","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:52:56"},{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Country Keys","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:52:56"},{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Cost Centres","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:52:56"},{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Vendors","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:52:56"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:52:56"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"19","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DDIC","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:52:56"}]},{"question":{"ID":"20","Question":"What are the valid attributes of a domain","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Label","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:54:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Length","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:54:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Fixed Values","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:54:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Type","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:54:05"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:54:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:54:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:54:05"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"20","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DDIC","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 00:54:05"}]},{"question":{"ID":"21","Question":"What are the main functions of Data Dictionary","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"To insulate the developer from the database","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:00:09"},{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"To provide data security at the application level","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:00:09"},{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"To connect to the operating system","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:00:09"},{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"To support the creation and management of metadata","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:00:09"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:00:09"},{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:00:09"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"21","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DDIC","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:00:09"}]},{"question":{"ID":"22","Question":"Programs that extend beyond transactional limits and want to pass data should use:","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"22","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"SAP Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:02:21"},{"QuestionId":"22","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Tables","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:02:21"},{"QuestionId":"22","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"ABAP\/4 memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:02:21"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"22","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:02:21"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"22","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:02:21"}]},{"question":{"ID":"23","Question":"Which of the following is an invalid method of populating an internal table","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Insert ITAB","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:04:13"},{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Append","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:04:13"},{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Read Table ITAB","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:04:13"},{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Select * into Table ITAB from dbtab.","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:04:13"},{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"Collect","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:04:13"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:04:13"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"23","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:04:13"}]},{"question":{"ID":"24","Question":"Identify the clause that is used to suppress standard headers","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:14:59","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"No Standard Heading","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:05:22"},{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"No Standard Page Heading","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:05:22"},{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Suppress Standard","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:05:22"},{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"System>List>Save","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:05:22"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:05:22"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"24","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"ABAP","CreatedAt":"2013-07-03 01:05:22"}]},{"question":{"ID":"25","Question":"You have made changes to an existing table that contains data. What takes place when the Database Conversion utility is executed ?","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-08 00:08:55","ActiveStatus":""},"options":[{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Data in the table is automatically deleted and must be reloaded","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"The table in the database is renamed and eventually deleted","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The indexes for the table needs to manually be reconstructed in the ABAP Dictionary","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"The revised table in the ABAP\/4 Dictionary is activated","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"The table in the database is recreated","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"5","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"}],"meta":[{"QuestionId":"25","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"Database","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"DB","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"table","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","MetaKey":"tag","MetaValue":"Utility","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 14:30:42"}]}],"quiz_list":[{"QuizId":"3","Description":"ABAP Basics - 1","Count":"10","Level":"1","QuestionIds":"4,5,6,8,12,14,15,16,18,19","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:16:18","ActiveStatus":"X"},{"QuizId":"4","Description":"Database Fundamentals","Count":"5","Level":"2","QuestionIds":"7,9,13,17","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:16:21","ActiveStatus":"X"},{"QuizId":"5","Description":"ABAP Basics - 2","Count":"5","Level":"1","QuestionIds":"20,21,23,24","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 00:16:23","ActiveStatus":"X"}]}